Guide to the Luis Leal Papers, 1946-1985
Department of Special Collections
- Series 7: Reprint information
  - Subseries B: EL NACIONAL (México): Miscellaneous news papers tearsheets, 1958-1972
    - Jul. 1965-Dec. 1965 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Jan. 1966-June 1966 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Jul. 1966-Dec. 1966 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 1967-June 1967 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Jul. 1967-Dec. 1967 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Jan. 1968, Sept. 1969, May. 1970, Jul. 1972 (Box 170, Folder 4)